<!DOCTYPE Job SYSTEM "job.dtd">
<Job ShortName="FHor">
    <Description>
        She will star in a horror movie.
    </Description>
    <Performance>
        <Factor Stat="Charisma" Weight="1"/>
        <Factor Stat="Beauty" Weight="1"/>
        <Factor Stat="Confidence" Weight="1"/>
        <Factor Skill="Performance" Weight="3"/>

        <Mod>work.actress</Mod>

        <!-- good traits -->
        <Trait Name="Sexy Air" Value="22"/>    <!-- nice video -->
        <Trait Name="Agile" Value="20"/>
        <Trait Name="Cool Person" Value="10"/>
        <Trait Name="Audacity" Value="10"/>
        <Trait Name="Cute" Value="20"/>    <!-- Attractive to some -->
        <Trait Name="Exotic" Value="15"/>
        <Trait Name="Idol" Value="15"/>
        <Trait Name="Elegant" Value="10"/>
        <Trait Name="Beauty Mark" Value="5"/>

        <!-- bad traits -->
        <Trait Name="Mind Fucked" Value="-40"/>    <!-- too messed up -->
        <Trait Name="Nervous" Value="-15"/>    <!-- weakens performance -->
        <Trait Name="Shy" Value="-20"/>
        <Trait Name="Retarded" Value="-15"/>
    </Performance>

    <Gains XP="15" Skill="2">
        <Skill Name="Performance" Weight="2"/>
        <Stat Name="Charisma" Weight="1"/>
        <Stat Name="Confidence" Weight="1" Max="50" />

        <GainTrait Trait="Actress" >
            <TraitChangeAmount Value="20" Chance="25" />
            <Text>She has performed in enough scenes that she has become a good Actress.</Text>
        </GainTrait>

        <GainTrait Trait="Idol" >
            <TraitChangeAmount Value="75" Chance="20">
                <TraitChangeCondition What="JobPerformance" Lower="100" Upper="200" />
                <TraitChangeCondition What="Fame" Lower="50" Upper="100" />
            </TraitChangeAmount>
            <Text>Her talented and charismatic performances have got a large number of fans Idolizing her.</Text>
        </GainTrait>

        <GainTrait Trait="Cool Person" >
            <TraitChangeAmount Value="40" Chance="33">
                <TraitChangeCondition What="JobPerformance" Lower="100" Upper="200" />
                <TraitChangeCondition What="Agility" Lower="33" Upper="66" />
            </TraitChangeAmount>
            <Text>Performing in a horror flick makes ${name} a really Cool Person.</Text>
        </GainTrait>
    </Gains>

    <Config PrimaryAction="Performing" SecondaryAction="Fighting">
    </Config>

    <Messages>
        <Message Name="work">
            <Text>${name} played a part in a horror movie production.</Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="refuse">
            <Text>${name} refused to shoot a horror movie today.</Text>
        </Message>

        <Message Name="work.perfect">
            <Text Condition="stat:Age<25">
                She had been handpicked for the role of playing a young girl who,
                while exploring her abandoned mansion home alone, encounters something
                sinister lurking within its walls. In order to truly capture the essence
                of terror and unease that comes with this type of situation,
                the director needed someone who could exude innocence yet also project fear
                all at once - which ${name} did brilliantly! Her performance brought life to every single scene
                and helped build suspense throughout the entirety of the movie.  As such,
                it earned high praise from both critics and fans alike.
            </Text>

            <Text>
                She was required to play the role of a
                seductive woman who lured unsuspecting men into her lair - only for
                them to meet their untimely demise. As such, it called for her to be
                incredibly alluring and tantalizingly dangerous at the same time. She
                had to use every bit of charm and sexuality that she possessed to make
                the audience believe that any man would willingly follow her anywhere.
                Her costume played a significant part in creating the desired effect.
                It consisted of a tight, revealing dress that hugged her curves and
                left little to the imagination. Her hair was styled in a way that made
                her look both innocent and tempting, with flowing locks cascading down
                her back. To top it off, she wore high heels that added extra inches
                to her already impressive height, making her seem even more
                commanding.

                As the camera rolled, ${name} moved around the set with a
                sensual grace, using slow, deliberate movements to draw attention to
                her body. When she spoke, her voice was low and sultry, sending
                shivers down the spines of those watching. Every step she took seemed
                to ooze confidence and invitation, as if daring anyone to come closer.
                It wasn't just her physical appearance or mannerisms that were key to
                pulling off this scene; ${name}'s facial expressions also held great
                importance. They needed to convey a sense of danger mixed with desire
                - an intoxicating combination that left audiences captivated yet wary.
                As the tension built between her character and the unsuspecting
                victim, ${name}'s eyes gleamed with promise and threat, hinting at
                what was to come when the moment finally arrived for her to strike.
                Throughout the entire shoot, ${name} remained completely focused on
                delivering the performance required, pouring all of herself into every
                seductive gesture and sinister glance. In doing so, she created a
                character who was undeniably sexy but equally terrifying - a woman who
                could lure men to their doom without ever having to raise her voice in
                anger.
            </Text>

            <Text Condition="Aggressive">
                In one particular scene, she played the role of an enraged young woman
                who was hellbent on causing destruction and chaos around her. The
                atmosphere was tense with smoke filling up the air from burning
                objects that were being destroyed by her fury. Sweat dripped down her
                face as she furiously threw things around, screaming at the top of her
                lungs while her eyes burned with anger. Despite how intense the scene
                was, ${name} relished every moment of it, giving her all to make the
                character come alive on screen.
            </Text>

            <Text Condition="Slut">
                In this scene, she played the slutty girl who gets murdered gruesomely by her boyfriend after being caught cheating on him.
                She is perfect for this role. In fact, the clothes she wears in the scene are exactly how she arrived on set.
                No makeup or wardrobe changes were needed - she actually *is* the Slut the director envisioned.
                When she takes off her top revealing her breasts for all to see, it's like watching an actual sex tape come to life right there on screen.
                ${name} seemed somewhat disappointed that no actual intercourse occurred during filming,
                but nonetheless delivered an incredible performance filled with passion and intensity from start to finish!
            </Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="work.great">
            <Text Condition="stat:Age<25">
                She had been picked for the role of playing a young girl who,
                while exploring her abandoned mansion home alone, encounters something
                sinister lurking within its walls.  The character requires acting talent beyond her years
                and ${name} delivered flawlessly - captivating audiences with every scene she appeared in.
                Her portrayal of fear and terror was so convincingly realistic that it left many viewers feeling scared even after watching the film multiple times.
                Not only did she manage to convey strong emotion through facial expressions but also physical movements such as shaking limbs or wide eyes conveying absolute terror.
                This combination allowed for an intense atmosphere which kept people glued onto their seats until the end credits rolled
            </Text>
            <Text>
                In one particularly intense moment, she delivered her lines with such conviction that it sent chills down every viewer's spine.
                If the entire scene had been like this, it would have been the performance of the year. As it was, the
                scene was great, but not outstanding.
            </Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="work.good">
            <Text>
                As the camera rolled, she gave life to her character - a terrified and
                helpless victim of unspeakable horrors.
                Her facial expressions conveyed fear and panic perfectly, allowing viewers to fully immerse themselves in the story unfolding before their eyes.
                Though at times she may have fallen short of delivering an award-winning performance,
                it was clear that ${name} had put effort into getting into character.
                Despite some minor flaws, ${name}'s portrayal still proved effective
                in creating suspenseful moments that kept viewers hooked until
                the very end.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                In this particular scene, she found herself trapped in a dark room filled
                with cobwebs and dusty furniture.
                As she explored further into the unknown space,
                she began to hear strange sounds emanating from within its walls.
                Fearful for her life but determined not to give up without some sort
                of fight against whatever creature lurked inside this place, she slowly
                made her way towards where the noise originated...

                ${name} managed to deliver a solid performance full of fear
                and excitement which captivated viewers until its final moments.
                Overall, although far from perfect,
                this particular scene showcased her ability to create
                dynamic characters.
            </Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="work.ok">
            <Text>
                Though her acting wasn't terrible, it could have been better.
                The scene required ${name}'s character to seem terrified and paranoid; however, she simply seemed confused or distracted instead.
                Her facial expressions also lacked any real emotion or intensity that would have helped convey the desired effect.
                These shortcomings rendered the entire sequence less impactful than intended.
                Fortunately, other parts of the story made up for this lackluster performance by offering some truly frightening moments instead
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="Aggressive">
                ${name} played a part in a horror movie production.
                In one particular scene, she played the role of an enraged young woman
                who was hellbent on causing destruction and chaos around her.
                She pulled off the aggressive nature of the character convincingly;
                In fact, she hurt several crew members in a fury that was not at all an act.
                All in all, it was not exactly an award-winning performance but rather one
                that would be remembered because of its sheer violence and intensity.
            </Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="work.bad">
            <Text>
                She tried her best to convey the
                appropriate emotions for the role, but inside, she felt nothing but
                dread at being surrounded by such gruesome props and special effects.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                Unfortunately, her acting abilities were far from impressive.
                She lacked any emotion or expression as she delivered lines that were supposed to send shivers down viewers’
                spines but instead elicited nothing but snickering and giggles from the audience.
                Her performance was simply not up to par with what was expected from such an important role within the movie.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="Meek">
                In the scene, her character was meant to be a strong and confident woman who could take care of herself.
                However, her performance fell flat as she failed miserably at conveying these traits through body language and facial expressions alone.
                Instead of appearing brave and independent,
                she came across more like a timid girl afraid of everything around her - including herself.
                This made it difficult for viewers to believe that she was capable of handling dangerous situations without help from others.
            </Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="work.worst">
            <Text>
                Her portrayal of her character was lacking the desired
                emotional depth, and she failed to convey the intended sense of fear or
                terror that would have made for a more engaging and gripping scene.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                Her character was intended to be frightening and intimidating,
                but unfortunately her lackluster performance failed miserably at this goal.
                Instead of striking fear into the hearts of viewers,
                she merely came across as goofy and awkward, completely missing the mark with her delivery.
                The result was a very unintentionally funny scene that became more cringe-worthy than anything else.
            </Text>
        </Message>
    </Messages>
</Job>
