<!DOCTYPE Job SYSTEM "job.dtd">
<Job ShortName="FJOI">
    <Description>
        She will give jerk-off instructions to her viewers.
    </Description>
    <Performance>
        <Factor Stat="Charisma" Weight="2"/>
        <Factor Stat="Beauty" Weight="2"/>
        <Factor Stat="Confidence" Weight="1"/>
        <Factor Skill="Performance" Weight="1"/>
        <Factor Skill="Handjob" Weight="1"/>

        <Mod>work.actress</Mod>

        <!-- good traits -->
        <Trait Name="Sexy Air" Value="25"/>    <!-- nice video -->
        <Trait Name="Agile" Value="10"/>
        <Trait Name="Cool Person" Value="15"/>
        <Trait Name="Cute" Value="20"/>    <!-- Attractive to some -->
        <Trait Name="Exotic" Value="15"/>
        <Trait Name="Idol" Value="15"/>

        <!-- bad traits -->
        <Trait Name="Mind Fucked" Value="-40"/>    <!-- too messed up -->
        <Trait Name="Nervous" Value="-15"/>    <!-- weakens performance -->
        <Trait Name="Shy" Value="-20"/>
        <Trait Name="Retarded" Value="-15"/>
    </Performance>

    <Gains XP="15" Skill="2">
        <Skill Name="Performance" Weight="1" Max="33" />
        <Stat Name="Charisma" Weight="1" Max="50"/>
        <Stat Name="Confidence" Weight="1" Max="50" />
    </Gains>

    <Config PrimaryAction="Performing" SecondaryAction="Stripping">
    </Config>

    <Messages>
        <Message Name="work">
            <Text>${name} was filmed giving jerk-off instructions to her viewers.</Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="refuse">
            <Text>${name} refused to shoot a JOI movie today.</Text>
        </Message>

        <Message Name="work.perfect">
            <Text>
                She confidently delivered every line of sultry words
                that tantalized viewers into getting hard and stroking themselves for hours on end.
                With her voice full of promise and desire,
                each sentence dripped with eroticism as she encouraged them to take matters into their own hands.
                The combination of her sensual delivery and powerful words created an experience unlike any other; one which left even veteran masturbators begging for more!
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="Tsundere">
                She spoke in a tone that could be both playful and serious,
                teasing them with her words while making sure they were following orders properly.
                By alternating between flirty commands and strict demands,
                she managed to keep their attention focused solely on what she was saying rather than anything else around them.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                As a master of dirty talk, she managed to make countless viewers crave
                for more while pleasuring themselves with her sexy commands and moans.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                The camera zoomed in tightly on ${name}'s face while she spoke to them passionately about how they could please themselves better.
                Her soft brown hair cascaded down her back
                and accentuated her mesmerizing eyes.
                She spoke directly into the lens, making it feel like you were alone
                with only her guidance leading you through your fantasies.
                Each word exuded pure desire for what lies ahead—a journey into
                self-discovery fueled by pleasure itself!
                With such an irresistible presentation from someone so captivating,
                who wouldn't want to follow her instructions?
            </Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="work.great">
            <Text Condition="Meek|Shy">
                Despite her timid demeanor, she managed to captivate viewers with her seductive voice and hypnotizing gaze.
                Her soft tones and gentle touch encouraged men to let go of their inhibitions and get lost in the moment under her guidance.
                With every instruction given, audiences became more aroused as they followed along with anticipation and excitement.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                In the video, she wore a white shirt tied up above her waist,
                revealing her perky breasts and toned abs. Her long brown hair was
                styled in loose waves that cascaded down her back while she
                confidently directed viewers through each stroke. As she spoke, her
                lips curved into a sultry smile, making it clear that she enjoyed
                every second of guiding men towards ecstatic release.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                The video featured clips from different angles, showing off her body
                and seductive gaze. Her instructions were both playful and naughty
                as she directed viewers through each step with ease.
                Throughout the clip, it became clear why she is such a popular webcam model -
                her confidence, personality, and talent are truly captivating!
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="Sexy Air">
                As she spoke, her hand gracefully caressed her full breasts while
                her plump lips curved into a teasing smile. Her voice was seductive and
                captivating, inviting listeners to join in on the fun. The combination
                of her sultry words combined with alluring movements were enough to send viewers spiraling out of control.
            </Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="work.good">
            <Text Condition="stat:Beauty>75">
                As they watched, each stroke caused their hearts to beat faster while
                enjoying the visual stimulation provided by this gorgeous woman.
                She confidently spoke with authority as she guided men on how to properly pleasure themselves without shame or embarrassment.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                While the content of her video was fairly standard fare,
                she managed to make it sexy nonetheless.
                From her flirtatious mannerisms to sultry sounds,
                every element of her instructional clip exuded sexual energy that kept viewers glued to their screens.
            </Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="work.ok">
            <Text>
                While it wasn't the most thrilling or captivating display of erotica,
                her gentle commands and soothing voice managed to keep viewers entertained.
                Even though there wasn't much excitement involved, ${name} was able to provide enough guidance
                that viewers were able to enjoy themselves.
            </Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="work.bad">
            <Text>
                While attempting to be sexy and seductive, she ends up sounding like a robot instead.
                Her monotone voice fails to stimulate any feelings or emotions within you.
                You are left feeling nothing but disappointment after watching such an unsatisfying display.
                If only they could have found someone who knew what they were doing...
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="Nervous|Shy|Chaste">
                While she tried her best to give directions, it was obvious that she wasn't comfortable in front of the camera.
                She kept looking around nervously and stammering through her lines, making it difficult for viewers to follow along.
                At one point, she even forgot what she was supposed to say next.
                Overall, it was a cringe-worthy experience
                for both her and anyone watching who wished they could turn back time.
            </Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="work.worst">
            <Text>
                Her attempt at encouraging her viewers to masturbate isn't erotic at all. In fact,
                you are thinking of whether you might still make some money with this by selling
                the clip to a local priest, who is teaching his followers abstinence and that masturbation is evil.
                But then, do you really want to help this man?
            </Text>
        </Message>
    </Messages>
</Job>
