<!DOCTYPE Job SYSTEM "job.dtd">
<Job ShortName="FCmd" Title="Comedian">
    <Description>
        She will star in a comedy movie.
    </Description>

    <Config DefaultImage="Profile">
        <Enjoyment BaseEnjoyment="5" PrimaryAction="Performing" SecondaryAction="Social" />
        <Obedience Difficulty="20" Fear="0" Dignity="80" />
    </Config>

    <Performance>
        <Factor Stat="Charisma" Weight="2"/>
        <Factor Stat="Beauty" Weight="1"/>
        <Factor Stat="Confidence" Weight="1"/>
        <Factor Skill="Performance" Weight="2"/>

        <Mod>work.actress</Mod>

        <!-- good traits -->
        <Trait Name="Sexy Air" Value="22"/>    <!-- nice video -->
        <Trait Name="Agile" Value="20"/>
        <Trait Name="Cool Person" Value="10"/>
        <Trait Name="Audacity" Value="10"/>
        <Trait Name="Cute" Value="20"/>    <!-- Attractive to some -->
        <Trait Name="Exotic" Value="15"/>
        <Trait Name="Idol" Value="15"/>
        <Trait Name="Lolita" Value="10"/>
        <Trait Name="Elegant" Value="10"/>
        <Trait Name="Beauty Mark" Value="5"/>
        <Trait Name="Social Drinker" Value="5"/>   <!-- relaxed -->

        <!-- bad traits -->
        <Trait Name="Mind Fucked" Value="-40"/>    <!-- too messed up -->
        <Trait Name="Nervous" Value="-25"/>    <!-- weakens performance -->
        <Trait Name="Shy" Value="-30"/>
        <Trait Name="Retarded" Value="-30"/>
    </Performance>

    <Gains XP="15" Skill="2">
        <Skill Name="Performance" Weight="2"/>
        <Stat Name="Charisma" Weight="1"/>
        <Stat Name="Confidence" Weight="1" Max="50" />

        <GainTrait Trait="Actress" >
            <TraitChangeAmount Value="20" Chance="25" />
            <Text>She has performed in enough scenes that she has become a good Actress.</Text>
        </GainTrait>

        <GainTrait Trait="Charming" >
            <TraitChangeAmount Value="33" Chance="25" />
            <Text>Her ability to tell jokes in any situation make ${name} quite Charming.</Text>
        </GainTrait>

        <GainTrait Trait="Idol" >
            <TraitChangeAmount Value="75" Chance="20">
                <TraitChangeCondition What="JobPerformance" Lower="100" Upper="200" />
                <TraitChangeCondition What="Fame" Lower="50" Upper="100" />
            </TraitChangeAmount>
            <Text>Her talented and charismatic performances have got a large number of fans Idolizing her.</Text>
        </GainTrait>

        <GainTrait Trait="Cool Person" >
            <TraitChangeAmount Value="40" Chance="33">
                <TraitChangeCondition What="JobPerformance" Lower="100" Upper="200" />
                <TraitChangeCondition What="Agility" Lower="33" Upper="66" />
            </TraitChangeAmount>
            <Text>Performing in a comedy movie makes ${name} a really Cool Person.</Text>
        </GainTrait>
    </Gains>

    <Messages>
        <Message Name="work">
            <Text>${name} played a part in a comedy production.</Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="refuse">
            <Text>${name} refused to shoot a comedy movie today.</Text>
        </Message>

        <Message Name="work.perfect">
            <Text>
                From her very first take, you could tell that she had nailed her lines down pat, bringing laughs from everyone who watched them unfold.
                Her physical comedy skills were top-notch too; no matter how many takes they did of a certain scene,
                she always managed to come up with something fresh that kept everyone entertained.
                The end result is a truly perfect comedy scene.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                Her timing and delivery were impeccable, eliciting laughter from both cast and crew alike.
                No matter how difficult the line or situation might be, ${name} always found a way to make it funny with her clever wit and charisma.
                It truly was a sight to behold!
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="Titanic Tits|Abnormally Large Boobs|Massive Melons|Giant Juggs">
                Her timing and delivery were impeccable, eliciting laughter from both cast and crew alike. Most striking was how deftly she used her large chest as part of her comedic toolkit; her bouncing breasts became a source of many jokes throughout the scene.
                The result? A perfectly crafted comedy scene that had everyone rolling in the aisles!
            </Text>
            <Text>
                She had a unique ability to make even the most mundane tasks entertaining and funny to watch.
                Her facial expressions and body language were perfect for creating humor out of any situation, whether she was having trouble with a prop or playing off one-liners delivered by other cast members.
                Everyone involved in the production couldn't help but laugh along with her throughout every take – truly making it a perfect comedy scene!
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="Slut">
                She didn't have to act much to play the role of
                a slutty girlfriend who gets drunk and causes chaos while out with friends - because in real life
                she was already doing it! Her drunken behavior was so convincing that even
                the cast members couldn't tell if she was playing
                or really getting intoxicated off camera; it made for some truly hilarious moments
                on-screen which will have viewers laughing nonstop.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="Singer">
                The director made good use of her talents by having her sing various catchy songs throughout the show.
                Each performance left audiences in stitches as
                they laughed along to her hilarious lyrics and melodies.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="Mute">
                Though she is mute, her facial expressions are enough to convey any emotion needed.
                Without saying a word, ${name} manages to make people laugh and feel happy inside.
                The audience loves watching ${name}'s hilarious antics without needing verbal cues.
                No wonder why ${name} is such a beloved actor - even if she can't speak!
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="Dwarf">
                Despite being a Dwarf, ${name} proved to be more than capable of producing belly-aching laughs with her outrageous antics on camera.
                Her timing was spot-on and her physical gags were executed flawlessly, making even the most mundane scenarios seem hilarious through ${name}'s eyes.
                Everyone involved in this production can attest to just how perfect this little person truly was for her roles!
            </Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="work.great">
            <Text Condition="Charming|Charismatic">
                She brought a natural charm to each performance, making her characters believable and relatable despite being exaggerated or even ridiculous at times.
                Her comedic timing was spot-on, allowing her to deliver punchlines perfectly.
                No matter what role she played or how silly the situation got,
                ${name} always managed to make audiences laugh out loud without ever becoming too goofy or unrealistic
            </Text>
            <Text>
                She was known for being able to make any joke work, no matter how bad it might be.
                Her timing, delivery, and comedic ability were so spot-on that each take resulted in laughter from the cast and crew alike.
                No matter what situation she found herself in, ${name} always managed to find a way out of it while still keeping everyone entertained.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="Titanic Tits|Abnormally Large Boobs|Massive Melons|Giant Juggs">
                Her breasts were so large that they became an integral part of her comedic timing - providing both visual humor and physical gags.
                Every time she moved or made a joke, those big boobs bounced along
                with her - turning what would have otherwise been dull material into something hilarious!
            </Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="work.good">
            <Text Condition="Titanic Tits|Abnormally Large Boobs|Massive Melons|Giant Juggs">
                Throughout most of the movie she relied heavily on her large breasts for comedic relief;
                whether it was dropping something while trying to cover them up or bouncing around wildly when running away from someone -
                her large chest provided plenty of opportunities for laughter throughout each scene.
                While most of these moments were certainly amusing, they sometimes felt a bit forced and didn't always land well with audiences.
                Ultimately though, viewers still enjoyed what they saw thanks partly due to the fact that no matter what happened during those moments
                of comic genius - one thing remained constant:
                the undeniable power of big tits!
            </Text>
            <Text>
                ${name} worked as an actress filming comedy scenes.
                Her timing was impeccable, never missing a beat even when delivering jokes that were borderline corny at best.
                The audience could tell she put all her effort into every role she took on, which made them appreciate her performances more than ever before.
                Even though some gags weren't exactly funny,
                they still managed to elicit laughs from those watching due to how hard she tried making sure everything came out right.
                In short, viewers got an entertaining experience thanks largely to ${name}'s dedication towards her craft.
            </Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="work.ok">
            <Text>
                Her performance wasn't bad per se; however, there were noticeable flaws that made it far from perfect.
                There were occasional moments where she struggled with lines or forgot a key part of her character's personality,
                taking away from the overall effectiveness of each take.
                Nonetheless, despite these small hiccups here and there,
                she still brought plenty laughter out of audiences everywhere with her funny antics
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="Titanic Tits|Abnormally Large Boobs|Massive Melons|Giant Juggs">
                Throughout most of the movie she relied heavily on her large breasts for comedic relief;
                whether it was dropping something while trying to cover them up or bouncing around wildly when running away from someone -
                her large chest provided plenty of opportunities for laughter throughout each scene.
                While these moments were certainly amusing at times, they often felt somewhat forced and didn't always land well with audiences.
                Ultimately though, viewers still enjoyed what they saw thanks largely due to the fact that no matter what happened during those moments
                of comic genius - one thing remained constant:
                the undeniable power of big tits!
            </Text>
            <Text>
                One day, during the filming of her big scene, she forgot all her lines
                and tried to improvise with some hilarious punchlines that left
                everyone on set rolling with laughter - except for the director who
                had no idea what was going through her mind!
            </Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="work.bad">
            <Text>
                ${name}'s comedic timing was off, and she often missed cues or forgot lines during shooting.
                The end result was a very awkward performance that made everyone cringe at times.
                She tried hard but ultimately fell short of expectations in terms of quality.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                Her performance was awkward at best, consisting mostly of fumbling words, facial expressions, and clumsiness that made for an uncomfortable watch.
                Even though she tried hard to make things work out during filming, the results were less than desirable.
                The director had to spend hours editing and re-shooting certain parts to salvage this disaster of a scene.
            </Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="work.worst">
            <Text Condition="stat:Beauty<33">
                If she were pretty, maybe it wouldn't have been too bad that her comedic timing was non-existent.
                If she were funny, the scene could have been decent despite her face.

                Alas, she was neither.
            </Text>

            <Text>
                She tells a joke. Then she starts to explain it. Then she realizes that she forgot the punchline.
                Repeat this process ten times, and you get the worst attempt at comedy ever recorded.
            </Text>
        </Message>
    </Messages>
</Job>
