<!DOCTYPE Job SYSTEM "job.dtd">
<Job ShortName="FStp">
    <Description>
        She will perform in a strip tease scene.
    </Description>

    <Config DefaultImage="Strip">
        <Enjoyment BaseEnjoyment="5" PrimaryAction="Stripping" SecondaryAction="Performing" />
        <Obedience Difficulty="10" Dignity="15" />
        <Pleasure Amount="5" SkillMin="5" BaseValue="5" Skill="Strip" />
    </Config>

    <Performance>
        <Factor Stat="Charisma" Weight="1"/>
        <Factor Stat="Beauty" Weight="1"/>
        <Factor Skill="Performance" Weight="1"/>
        <Factor Skill="Strip" Weight="2"/>
        <Mod>work.pornstar</Mod>
        <Trait Name="Clumsy" Value="-15" />
        <Trait Name="Manly" Value="-10" />
    </Performance>

    <Gains XP="15" Skill="3">
        <Skill Name="Performance" Weight="2" />
        <Skill Name="Strip" Weight="1" />
        <Stat Name="Charisma" Weight="1" Max="50"/>

        <GainTrait Trait="Sexy Air" >
            <TraitChangeAmount Value="60" Chance="25">
                <TraitChangeCondition What="JobPerformance" Lower="150" Upper="200" />
            </TraitChangeAmount>
            <Text>${name} has been stripping for so long, when she walks, it seems her clothes just want to fall off. (+Sexy Air)</Text>
        </GainTrait>

        <GainTrait Trait="Idol" >
            <TraitChangeAmount Value="25" Chance="20">
                <TraitChangeCondition What="JobPerformance" Lower="100" Upper="200" />
                <TraitChangeCondition What="Fame" Lower="50" Upper="100" />
            </TraitChangeAmount>
            <Text>${name} has become an Idol.</Text>
        </GainTrait>

        <LoseTrait Trait="Chaste">
            <TraitChangeAmount Value="50" Chance="50" />
            <Text>Stripping in front of the camera (and the studio crew) has helped ${name} overcome her Chasteness.</Text>
        </LoseTrait>
    </Gains>


    <!--
    ### Instruction:
Scene: Striptease
Tags: Slut
Quality: Perfect

### Response:

### Instruction:
Scene: Striptease
Tags: Big Boobs
Quality: Worst

### Response:
${name} worked as an actress filming strip tease scenes.
Her busty figure made many men drool, but unfortunately it wasn't enough to cover up her lackluster performance.
No matter how much skin she revealed, there remained something off about her movements - almost robotic in nature.
Though they were technically following choreographed steps correctly, something just didn't feel right when watching them dance around stage...
perhaps too mechanical for someone who should be able to exude passion more naturally than machines do?
No matter how hard they tried or how long they practiced their routine ahead of time - nothing could save this scene from becoming unwatchable due
to its complete lack of authenticity from start to end. It truly was one scene where everything went wrong despite having so much going right initially.
-->

    <Messages>
        <Message Name="work">
            <Text>${name} worked as an actress filming strip tease scenes.</Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="refuse">
            <Text>${name} refused to strip on film today.</Text>
        </Message>

        <Message Name="work.perfect">
            <Text>${name} is so in love with her body, she strips erotically making the best Perfect Art.</Text>
            <Text>
                She knew exactly what she was doing and took great pleasure in showing off her curves for all to see.
                Her moves were smooth as silk and hypnotizingly sensual; every move had its own rhythm,
                each action accompanied by a sultry look into the camera lens that left viewers wanting more.
                Her confidence shone brightly throughout each performance making it hard not to get lost
                in the moment while witnessing first hand such an incredibly sexy spectacle!
                It goes without saying that ${name} proved herself time and again why she'll always remain one of your hottest stars.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                Everything clicked together perfectly when ${name} took off her clothes.
                From subtle glances towards potential partners off-camera to small gestures of seduction on stage;
                each move spoke volumes about her character's personality without ever having to utter a word.
                Everyone could tell that this was going to be an epic showdown between two powerful forces - lust vs innocence -
                and ${name}'s portrayal left us all wanting more. Her performance was simply stunning!
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="stat:Beauty>90">
                Her slender form and natural grace made everyone want to watch her intently when she took off her clothes on screen.
                The way she moved her hips while dancing around slowly undressing herself sent shivers down spines everywhere--even straight women couldn't help but feel aroused by this woman's power over them just through her presence alone!
                Once fully naked, her viewers were left speechless by the sight before their eyes;
                there was nothing else like it anywhere else on Earth (or beyond).
                Everything about her seemed perfect--from head to toe--and all anyone could do was sit back and enjoy the show.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="Assassin|Adventurer|Heroine|Brawler|Strong|Aggressive|Merciless|Sadistic|Yandere|Tsundere|Dominatrix">
                She had a knack for seducing men using only her body and words.
                As soon as they saw her perform on stage or camera, they couldn't take their eyes off of her.
                Each move was calculated perfectly, each glance seductive and dangerous at once.
                Even those who didn’t want to be seduced by her found themselves unable to resist.
                It was truly amazing what ${name} could do with just a few simple actions.
                Her talent was undeniable and impossible to ignore;
                she was sure to leave audiences breathless every time she performed one of these sexy routines.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="Flat Chest|Small Boobs|Petite Breasts">
                Dressed head to toe in lingerie, she slowly peeled away each article of clothing
                until only her small breasts were exposed for the camera. As she moved about seductively
                on stage while doing so, viewers could not help but be mesmerized by her beauty and graceful demeanor.
                The entire audience was captivated by every move she made - from subtle gestures to dramatic poses that left little doubt
                in anyone’s mind regarding who was truly deserving of such attention. It was clear that with just one glance
                at ${name} you would instantly feel overwhelmed with desire and longing –
                something which makes any man wish they could spend even more time admiring her stunning features!
            </Text>
            <Text>
                ${name}'s voluptuous figure commanded attention everywhere she went; however, none were able to capture her true beauty quite like the camera did in this scene.
                Viewers will be treated with a sight unlike any other in terms of its eroticism and raw sexual appeal - perfectly capturing the essence of ${name}.
                Her every movement conveyed confidence and power while still maintaining an air of innocence about it all - something few women can pull off effectively without looking cheap or trashy instead.
                It's safe to say that this particular striptease performance will become forever embedded deep within many hearts and minds alike - serving as a testament to ${name}‘s undeniable magnetism whenever cameras start rolling
            </Text>
            <Text>
                She was able to captivate viewers' attention from start to finish through her sultry glances and playful gestures,
                showcasing the perfect blend between sensuality and mystery that kept people guessing until the very end.
                In addition to being incredibly sexy throughout each scene,
                viewers also enjoyed seeing just how comfortable ${name} felt within her own skin - making for one hell of an enjoyable watch indeed.
                With such skilled performances under her belt,
                it comes as no surprise why so many were left wanting more after witnessing what kind of magic ${name} could create on screen!
            </Text>
            <Text>
                In this particular scene, she appeared wearing nothing but silk robes - leaving viewers hungry
                for more as they waited eagerly until finally seeing what lay beneath those luxurious fabrics...and boy oh boy did it deliver!
                The sight of ${name} slowly removing each piece of clothing one by one was absolutely exquisite;
                each motion graceful and sensual.
                As if all else wasn't enough already - once fully naked on screen -${name} began gyrating her hips seductively
                while swaying back forth like some sort of ancient goddess come alive right then and there
                before our very eyes.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="Flexible|Agile|stat:Agility>80">
                In this particular scene,
                she performed a sexy pole dance that showcased both her impressive flexibility and incredible body.
                The camera captured every sensual moment in slow motion, allowing viewers to appreciate each fluid motion and tight squeeze as if they were right there next to her.
                Her gorgeous curves moved effortlessly through the air, turning heads wherever she went.
                Everything combined perfectly, creating an unforgettable experience for all who watched on -
                one which left no doubt in their mind that ${name} was truly capable of stealing anyone's heart away with just one look!
            </Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="work.great">
            <Text>${name} greatly teased the camera by slowly stripping of her clothes with many kisses.</Text>
            <Text>
                ${name} has always been known for having big boobs, and she puts them front center stage in this strip tease scene.
                As soon as she starts taking off her clothes you can tell that she knows what she's doing. Her hips move sexy while
                the camera zooms in on her curves. Her hands caress every inch of her body before finally finishing with two perfect breasts!
                The way she plays with herself makes you wonder if you should join in too...
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="stat:beauty<50">
                Although not classically beautiful nor having a supermodel-like physique,
                the way in which she moved was sexy.
                Each slow undulation had been choreographed so gracefully you could tell that hours were spent practicing each move until perfection was reached -
                leaving little room for mistakes when cameras started rolling.
                Furthermore, unlike other performers who simply disrobed and called it day – here was someone who knew exactly what she wanted from her audience members:
                to be aroused and titillated by an erotic display of skillful dance moves combined with artful nudity on stage.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                She was able to captivate viewers' attention from start to finish through her sultry glances and playful gestures,
                showcasing a blend between sensuality and mystery that kept people guessing until the very end.
                In addition to being sexy throughout each scene,
                viewers also enjoyed seeing just how comfortable ${name} felt within her own skin.
            </Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="work.good">
            <Text Condition="Singer">${name} was good with the chosen music to strip with. She even sang with the songs.</Text>
            <Text>
                She ${name} was able to exude sexiness while still appearing shy and innocent at heart,
                which added an extra layer of intrigue as she slowly peeled away piece by piece until finally revealing herself completely nude.
                Even though this particular scene may not have been overly risqué by today's standards,
                it definitely left viewers wanting more
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="Shy|Meek">
                Her timid nature made it difficult for her to express herself fully when performing on stage but despite this challenge,
                she managed to put on an impressive show every time thanks mainly due to her natural beauty and talent for dancing .
                Even though some viewers may have wished they saw something wilder from this shy girl - they couldn't deny the fact that what they got exceeded their expectations by far!
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="stat:Beauty<50">
                While her looks may not compare to some of the more famous sex symbols,
                one thing is certain - she knows how to put on a good show!
                Every move was choreographed perfectly from start to finish;
                she moved gracefully across stage and gave viewers exactly what they wanted without ever missing a beat.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                This time around, she was tasked with doing something more than just showing off her body - ${name} had to showcase her pole dancing skills too!
                Although she looked good doing it, there was still room for improvement since some moves came across as
                awkward rather than smooth and graceful like they should have been.
                Apart from these minor shortcomings, she delivered a good performance.
            </Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="work.ok">
            <Text>${name} did ok today. She was distracted by the other actions around her.</Text>
            <Text>
                The scene was nothing special, but it got the job done.
                She wasn't the best at stripping, but she knew what she was doing and managed
                to keep her clothes off long enough for viewers to get their money's worth.
                This type of performance isn't exactly award-winning material, but if you need someone who will
                do their job without too much fuss then ${name} may be just right for your project!
            </Text>
            <Text>
                Although she wasn't bad at stripping, there wasn't anything particularly special about her performance either.
                She had some basic moves down but lacked any real flair or personality that would make someone want to watch her dance again and again.
                It was just enough for the job though – nothing more than average quality work from this particular actress.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                The pole dancing routine she performed was impressive but failed to leave a lasting impression.
                Her moves were basic, lacking any real finesse,
                and when her clothes finally came off, viewers weren't left with much more than just another naked woman on screen.
            </Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="work.bad">
            <Text>${name} quickly striped off her clothes, acting like this was her times being processed at the jail.</Text>
            <Text Condition="Clumsy|Dojikko">
                ${name} began to take off her clothes slowly. Not because she was particularly sensual about it, it just
                took her three tries to open her bra. "Cut!" comes the instruction from the director. "Let's try this again."

                This time, everything seems to go smoothly, until her heels get entangled in her panties and she falls over.
                The director sighs, looking at ${name}'s bloody nose. "I guess we need to work with the footage we have now."
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="Titanic Tits|Abnormally Large Boobs|Massive Melons|Giant Juggs|Big Boobs|Busty Boobs">
                Her busty figure made many men drool, but unfortunately it wasn't enough to cover up her lackluster performance.
                No matter how much skin she revealed, there remained something off about her movements - almost robotic in nature.
                While ${name}'s body certainly had potential for greatness; unfortunately her acting skills couldn't measure up to them -
                making for yet another forgettable strip tease experience overall.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                She was supposed to take her time removing pieces of clothing,
                dance seductively for viewers while doing so, and show off her assets along the way.
                Unfortunately none of these things happened;
                Instead she quickly stripped off everything in one go - leaving little room for excitement or appreciation from either audience members or critics alike.
            </Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="work.worst">
            <Text>${name} is the worst stripper you have EVER seen. Way to shy to even look up and she blushed the entire remakes.</Text>
            <Text Condition="Chaste|Shy|Nervous">
                ${name} looks so uncomfortable when the director orders her to take her clothes off that you imagine
                even blind people would be turned off by this scene.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="Chaste|Shy|Nervous">>
                She was hired to perform a sexy striptease,
                but ended up being too timid to even show her full chest let alone anything else.
                The director became increasingly frustrated when she couldn't get what she wanted out of her lead actress.
                In fact, it took several takes before finally getting some decent shots where you could barely make out parts of her body through all the clothes that covered it.
                By then though, everyone involved just wanted to move onto something else
            </Text>
            <Text>
                Unfortunately, her performance failed miserably due to her lack of acting ability and poor facial expressions throughout the entire shoot.
                The director was left with no choice but to cut out most of her footage entirely in order to save face with
                audiences who didn't deserve such an atrocity on their screens.
            </Text>
        </Message>

        <Message Name="post-work-event">
            <Text Condition="Performance < 100 ^ stat:Beauty < 33">
                At the end of the filming, the director looks at you apologetically. "I've tried", she says, "but
                I think ${name} is just too ugly for this"
            </Text>
        </Message>
    </Messages>
</Job>
