<!DOCTYPE Job SYSTEM "job.dtd">
<Job ShortName="FLes">
    <Description>
        She will do a lesbian scene.
    </Description>

    <Performance>
        <Factor Stat="Beauty" Weight="1"/>
        <Factor Stat="Charisma" Weight="2"/>
        <Factor Skill="Performance" Weight="2"/>
        <Factor Skill="Lesbian" Weight="1"/>
        <Mod>work.pornstar</Mod>
        <Trait Name="Lesbian" Value="10" />
        <Trait Name="Straight" Value="-10" />
    </Performance>

    <Gains XP="15" Skill="3">
        <Skill Name="Performance" Weight="2" />
        <Skill Name="Lesbian" Weight="1" Max="75"/>

        <GainTrait Trait="Porn Star" >
            <TraitChangeAmount Value="40" Chance="50">
                <TraitChangeCondition What="JobPerformance" Lower="100" Upper="200" />
            </TraitChangeAmount>
            <Text>She has performed in enough sex scenes that she has become a well known Porn Star.</Text>
        </GainTrait>

        <GainTrait Trait="Nimble Tongue" >
            <TraitChangeAmount Value="100" Chance="33">
                <TraitChangeCondition What="JobPerformance" Lower="150" Upper="200" />
            </TraitChangeAmount>
            <Text>Making love to another woman regularly has forced ${name} to develop a Nimble Tongue.</Text>
        </GainTrait>

        <GainTrait Trait="Fake Orgasm Expert">
            <TraitChangeAmount Value="40" Chance="33">
                <TraitChangeCondition What="Libido" Lower="50" Upper="80" />
            </TraitChangeAmount>
            <Text>She has become quite the Faker.</Text>
        </GainTrait>

        <GainTrait Trait="Idol" >
            <TraitChangeAmount Value="15" Chance="20">
                <TraitChangeCondition What="JobPerformance" Lower="100" Upper="200" />
                <TraitChangeCondition What="Fame" Lower="50" Upper="100" />
            </TraitChangeAmount>
            <Text>${name} has become an Idol.</Text>
        </GainTrait>

        <LoseTrait Trait="Chaste">
            <TraitChangeAmount Value="50" Chance="50" />
            <Text>She has been filmed having sex so often that she is no longer Chaste.</Text>
        </LoseTrait>

        <LoseTrait Trait="Straight">
            <TraitChangeAmount Value="50" Chance="50">
                <TraitChangeCondition What="Lust" Lower="50" Upper="80" />
            </TraitChangeAmount>
            <Text>Having enjoyed the love of another women many times on set,
                ${name} realizes that she is not just turned on by men.</Text>
        </LoseTrait>
    </Gains>

    <Config PrimaryAction="PORNSTAR" SecondaryAction="SEX" CanBeForced="1">
        <LustInfluence Amount="25" SkillMin="20" BaseValue="5" Skill="Lesbian" />
    </Config>

    <Messages>
        <Message Name="work">
            <Text>${name} worked as an actress filming lesbian scenes.</Text>
        </Message>

        <Message Name="work.perfect">
            <Text>${name} doesn't care who she works with. She always gives a Perfect scene.</Text>
            <Text Condition="Straight">
                ${name} is an amazing actress. Even though she very much prefers fucking men, as soon
                as the director yells "Action!" she starts eating out her co-star with such vigor that you
                fear she might not be able to walk for the next hours. This is going to be one hell of a scene.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="Titanic Tits|Abnormally Large Boobs|Massive Melons|Giant Juggs|Big Boobs|Busty Boobs">
                ${name} strutted confidently onto the set, dressed in a provocative ensemble of lingerie and sheer stockings that accentuated her voluptuous form.
                Surrounded by the serenity of nature beneath the canopy of a towering tree, the cameras rolled as ${name} locked lips with a stunning woman.
                Their passionate and eager kisses quickly escalated into a sensual embrace, with their hands roaming all over each other's bodies.
                They undressed one another slowly, revealing their naked forms bathed in the warm sunlight.
                ${name} then knelt down and began to explore her partner's body, her tongue to darting and flicking between her legs with expert precision.
                Her partner writhed and moaned in ecstasy, begging for more as ${name} brought her to unparalleled heights of pleasure.
                It was an amazing performance.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="Slut">
                She really got into her role as a dirty slut and went above and beyond what was expected from her to make sure every frame of footage was perfect!
                Her enthusiasm for getting down and dirty with other women made for some incredible performances that will stay engraved in viewers' memories forever!
            </Text>
            <Text>
                Her partner was incredibly beautiful, and ${name} couldn’t help but admire her stunning form as they began their love making session together.
                The chemistry between them was palpable, which translated into some truly magnificent moments in front of the camera.
                Every touch, every caress, every kiss was filled with such intensity that even viewers could feel themselves being drawn into this world of pure sexual desire.
                And when it finally ended, there was nothing left but pure satisfaction – both physically and emotionally.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="skill:Lesbian>90^skill:OralSex>90">
                ${name} has mastered the art of Cunnilingus.
                During this particular scene she managed to bring her partner to climax three times over in just a few minutes.
                It was quite an amazing feat, leaving the director speechless and everyone else on set thoroughly impressed by her skills.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                During this scene, her passionate performance will give viewers goosebumps when they watch her intense lovemaking unfold before their eyes.
                She brought her partner multiple orgasms throughout the scene, leaving no doubt about how much she enjoyed giving pleasure.
                Her enthusiasm and skillful technique made for a perfect scene that will be remembered fondly by fans for years to come
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="Fake Orgasm Expert|Fast Orgasms">
                During her shoot she achieved multiple orgasms in rapid succession, leaving the audience in awe at such a feat.
                She made it look effortless as she moaned loudly while writhing in pleasure from each powerful release.
                The resulting scene was truly breathtaking; something that would be remembered by all who witnessed it!
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="Porn Star">
                ${name} is one of the most talented and experienced performers in the industry.
                Her ability to make every scene look genuine and believable earned her high praise among directors and viewers alike.
                She knows exactly when to use a certain move or technique, making sure that every detail in every shot looks perfect – even down to the slightest facial expressions!
                With such skillful workmanship, it's no surprise why fans continue flocking towards her work.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="Flat Chest|Small Boobs|Petite Breasts">
                ${name}'s chest might not be large but that doesn't stop her from giving an amazing performance! She's got great technique and knows how to please her partners.
                Even viewers who prefer more well-endowed women will find themselves enthralled by the passion and energy between these two ladies.
                With each caress, kiss, and moan captured on camera, anyone watching can tell that they are genuinely enjoying themselves; their connection is undeniable.
                Their chemistry is so strong that it almost feels like you're right there in the room watching them make sweet love!
            </Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="work.great">
            <Text>${name} pleased her lover in amazing ways.</Text>
            <Text Condition="Straight">
                ${name} really prefers dick over pussy, but she is a competent actress and does not let it show in
                the scene. In fact, the end result is a pretty great movie clip.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="Straight">
                ${name} is notably more comfortable working with male actors than females,
                but that doesn't stop her from delivering a fantastic performance in this particular scene.
                Despite her personal preference for penetrative sex,
                she skillfully portrays the character of a woman engaging in cunnilingus with an impressive level of enthusiasm and believability.
                The final product is a high-quality movie clip that is sure to leave viewers satisfied.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="Clumsy">
                Despite her initial clumsiness, ${name} was able to find her rhythm and move with more natural ease as the scene progressed.
                The passion between her and her female partner was undeniably palpable, as they locked eyes and moved in sync with one another.
                The chemistry they shared was captivating, making for a truly great lesbian sex scene that left viewers eager for more.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                Her partner was gorgeous and their chemistry was undeniable;
                their lovemaking was passionate and intense, leaving viewers wanting more.
                Even though there were times when things got too hot to handle between them,
                they managed to keep going until they reached orgasm together in perfect synchronicity.
                It truly was an amazing scene!
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="Big Boobs|Busty Boobs">
                As soon as she took off her clothes, the audience could tell that this was going to be a good scene.
                Her breasts were perfect, firm and round, begging to be touched by eager hands.
                The camera moved closer and closer until all one could see was her face; full of passion and desire.
                They kissed passionately before moving onto other areas of each others bodies.
                With every touch, every stroke, it became clearer how much these two loved each other.
                It was a truly mesmerizing experience watching them perform together on screen.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="Slut">
                Her reputation for being slutty followed her from set to set,
                which made for some very hot lesbian action when cameras rolled on her shoot today!
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="Fat|Plump">
                Even though she was far from model-like, her enthusiasm and willingness to explore made
                her performance more than worthwhile. The two women had great chemistry on screen and
                their intimate moments were captured beautifully by the cameras.
                They were able to bring out each other's best features while creating some memorable moments
                that will be sure to leave an impression on viewers everywhere.
            </Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="work.good">
            <Text>${name} gave several good orgasm's to her lover.</Text>
            <Text Condition="Straight">
                Despite being Straight, ${name} gave a decent performance in this Lesbian
                scene.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                Despite not having much experience working together, the pair managed to create some decent chemistry between them,
                leading to some nice shots capturing the intensity of their love making.
                Though the scene wasn't perfect, it still looked good enough for viewers to enjoy watching it.
            </Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="work.ok">
            <Text>${name} didn't care for her assigned actress, she did an ok job.</Text>
            <Text Condition="Straight">
                ${name} is only interested in men, and is not quite able to hide her revulsion
                while performing with another woman. Still, with some clever editing a halfway
                decent scene could be produced.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="Shy">
                ${name} worked as a pornstar performing in Lesbian scenes.
                She was initially shy around her partner, but once they started kissing and exploring one another
                physically, ${name} seemed to loosen up a bit. While she may not have been super expressive or vocalized her pleasure,
                it was clear that ${name} did indeed enjoy herself in the end, resulting in an OK scene.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                ${name} worked as a porn star filming lesbian scenes.
                Though they tried their hardest, the lack of enthusiasm and chemistry between the women was noticeable on camera.
                The result was a less than desirable performance but still manageable enough for viewers to watch without discomfort.
                They were able to get through the scene with minimal issues thanks to some strategic editing from director.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                They had no chemistry whatsoever, but they still managed to pull off some pretty decent looking shots thanks to some creative editing from the director afterwards!
                In fact, if you didn't know any better you might think they were actually enjoying each other during those moments on screen!
            </Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="work.bad">
            <Text>${name} visually wasn't interested in her lover at all. Terrible scene.</Text>
            <Text Condition="Straight">
                ${name} is as Straight as they come, and her disgust with this Lesbian scene can
                be clearly seen on camera. The result is pretty terrible. Maybe you should find a
                girl who is more into this.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                ${name} was not so excited about her love making,
                and it showed through her lackluster performance during filming.
                The entire thing felt more like a chore than something passionate or enjoyable
                for both parties involved. Despite this, they managed to get through
                the scene without any major mishaps - except for perhaps some
                awkwardly timed moans that didn't quite sync up with the movements on
                screen.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="Zombie">
                ${name} worked as a pornstar filming lesbian scenes.
                ${name} did not show much interest in playing the role, and often seemed bored or uninterested during filming sessions.
                This resulted in a performance that could best be described as "zombie-like",
                with very little emotion or expression displayed throughout the entirety of production process.
            </Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="work.worst">
            <Text>${name} was totally horrible today. She was scorned for hours by the entire crew.</Text>
            <Text Condition="stat:Beauty<33^Straight">
                ${name} is really not very good at this at all.
                Her technique is unrefined and her face conveys absolute repulsion while her co-star is giving her oral pleasure.
                To make things even worse, she also has quite an Ugly appearance in general.
                The end product of this scene is just plain hideous and difficult to watch.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="Straight">
                ${name} looked like a fish out of water as she stumbled her way through this horrendous
                lesbian scene. It was painful to watch and even more so for those poor souls
                forced to be a part of it. Thankfully this debacle will soon be forgotten
                and buried deep within the depths of the internet, never to be seen again.
            </Text>
        </Message>

        <Message Name="disobey.free">
            <Text>${name} refused to perform in a Lesbian scene today.</Text>
            <Text Condition="Straight">
                "Eww, I'm not gonna do it with a woman", ${name} exclaims before leaving the set.
            </Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="disobey.slave.nice">
            <Text>
                ${name} refused to perform in an Lesbian scene today. Nice guy that you are, you let her be.
            </Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="disobey.slave.neutral">
            <Text>
                ${name} refused to perform in an Lesbian scene today. "That's not how I wanted this to be," you say,
                "but I've got bills to pay. Tie her up!"
            </Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="disobey.slave.evil">
            <Text>
                "No, I'm not doing this!", ${name} complains. Ignoring her pleading, your studio crew roughly ties her up. "It seems
                like a lesson in obedience is in order here", you say as you hand a gigantic dildo to the
                other actress actor. Turning to her with an evil grin on you face, you add "No foreplay, no lube!"
            </Text>
        </Message>

        <Message Name="forced-filming">
            <Text Condition="Performance>100">
                Given ${name}'s rather 'unenthusiastic' performance, the scene turned out decent enough.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="Performance<125^stat:Spirit<60">
                ${name} is just laying there, totally unresponsive except for a few whimpers and cries.
                Not a good scene.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="Performance<125^stat:Spirit>=60">
                Despite being tied up, ${name} managed to hurt the other actress. Needless to say, the scene
                turned out rather bad.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="Performance<50">
                While tying her up made it possible to film this scene, the result looks so bad that maybe you should
                have just sent her to the dungeon instead.
            </Text>
        </Message>
    </Messages>
</Job>
